http://www.addtimerecording.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Software
Time and Attendance Software Workforce Management Software Visitor Management Security Patrol TS4 System
Hardware
Biometric Facial Recognition Scanners Biometric Fingerprint Scanners Biometric Hand Scanners Palm Vein Scanners Proximity Card Readers
Services
Project Management Biometric Enrolment Training Support Packages Finance Options
About Us
Meet The Team What is Time and Attendance? What is Workforce Management? Solutions for Sectors FAQs Our Customers Blogs Case Studies
0
No products in the basket.
Products
Software
Time and Attendance Software Workforce Management Software Visitor Management Software Security Patrol TS4 System
Brands
Suprema Timy ZK Teco Others
Hardware
Biometric Facial Recognition Scanners Biometric Fingerprint Scanners Biometric Hand Scanners Palm Vein Scanners Proximity Card Readers
Clock Card Machines Security Patrol Systems Consumables
Clock Cards Ink Ribbons Proximity Fobs Card Racks
Services
Project Management Biometric Enrolment Training Support Packages Finance Options
About Us
Meet The Team What is Time and Attendance? What is Workforce Management? Solutions for Sectors FAQ’s Our Customers Blogs Case Studies
Shop Contact Us
sales@addtimerecording.co.uk
01942 272061
Privacy and how we use your data
Addtime Recording Company Limited as a ‘Data Processor’ gather and process your personal information in accordance with this privacy notice and in compliance with the relevant data protection Regulation and law. This notice provides you with the necessary information regarding your rights and obligations, and explains how, why and when we collect and process your personal data. Addtime Recording Company Limited registered office is at Levine House, 233 Wigan Road, Ashton-In-Makerfield, Wigan, Lancashire. WN4 9SR and we are a company registered in England and Wales under company number 02372726. Our designated Data Protection Officer/Appointed Person for the organisation is Tim Groves, and he can be contacted at 358 Garswood Road, Ashton in Makerfield, Wigan, Lancashire. WN4 0TZ. Do we use ‘cookies’? Yes. Cookies are small files that enable websites to remember certain information about the way you browse a website. They can help speed up the user experience (for example, by remembering previous items you’ve browsed) and make your browsing experience more personal. Cookies can also provide data through Google Analytics about site traffic and the way visitors use our site. Some cookies are used only for the duration of your visit (session cookies), some stay on your device and make online browsing faster or easier (permanent cookies) and some are third party cookies, used by trusted product or service providers or advertisers to track performance. We use cookies of all the above types – although we may not use all of them, all of the time. Do you have to accept cookies? No. You can change the way your device handles cookies by amending your bowser settings. Exactly how you do that varies from browser to browser (the process is, for example, slightly different depending on whether you are using Internet Explorer, Chrome or Firefox). You will have the choice of accepting all cookies, being notified when a cookie is about to be issued, or refusing all cookies. If you choose not to receive any cookies you may be unable to receive certain services and the website may not function properly – but you will still be able to browse our workforce management services, information and products. You can also opt out of cookie tracking on your device using your browser’s privacy settings. What personal information do we collect? Addtime Recording Company Limited processes your personal information to meet our legal, statutory and contractual obligations and to provide customers with a customised solution. We will never collect any unnecessary personal data from you and do not process your information in any way, other than already specified in this notice.When you order from us or ask us for a quote using the contact form on the Addtime website, we will ask for your name, email address, phone number, the nature of your enquiry and the number of staff you employ. This information will help us be better prepared for handling your query. The personal data that we collect from is always in relation to how you want your software to be set up from a simple time and attendance to a comprehensive workforce management database: –
Name Business Email Work Telephone Number Mobile Telephone Number
We collect information in the below ways: –
Website enquiries Digital marketing activity Telephone Enquiries Email Enquiries Cookies and usage data
How do we use your information? Legal Basis for Processing & Legitimate Interest Addtime Recording Company Limited takes your privacy very seriously and will never disclose, share or sell your data without your consent, unless required to do so by law. We only retain your data until a project is completed and for the purposes specified in this notice. Once a project has been completed both the database and your employees biometric profile will be stored on your server (either physical or virtual) and how safe it is will depend on your IT provider. Where you have consented to us providing you with promotional offers and marketing information, you are free to withdraw consent at any time. Our processing of your Data is done because it is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests in offering our customers the best and most relevant offers and products.
We collect your personal data to project manage the introduction of a time and attendance or workforce management solution into an organisation or to manage an upgrade of an existing system before installing onto your company server. We collect and store customer or prospect data for the purposes of marketing Addtime products and services to ensure you are always updated and informed. Our website is now enabled for e-commerce and as such has SSL encryption to protect personal details and your credit card details are protected by a third -party when ordering from our Shop
How do we protect your information? Addtime Recording Company Limited takes your privacy seriously and we take every reasonable measure and precaution to protect and secure your personal data. We work hard to protect you and your information from unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction and have several layers of security measures in place, including: –
Data is encrypted and backed up daily Firewalls for both our server and network Protective passwords Website SSL certificate Encrypted emails
Sharing and Disclosing your Personal Information We do not share or disclosure any of your personal information without your consent, other than for the purposes specified in this notice or where there is a legal requirement. We do not give, sell or transfer any information that could be used to identify you personally to any third party. From time to time, we may link to products or services offered by third parties. If we do, each party will have its own terms and conditions of use and its own privacy policies and you should check these before you use the third party site or buy a product or service from it. We are not liable for the content on any third party site. Consequences of not providing your data You are not obligated to provide your personal information to Addtime Recording Company Limited, however, as this information is required for us to provide you with our services/deliver your projects, we will not be able to offer some/all of our products or services without it. How long do we keep your data? Addtime Recording Company Limited only ever retains personal information for as long as a project requires it and we have strict review and retention policies in place to meet these obligations. Where you have consented to us using your details for direct marketing, we will keep such data on our CRM system until you notify us otherwise and/or withdraw your consent. Complaints, comments and corrections Addtime Recording Company Limited only processes your personal information in compliance with this privacy notice and in accordance with the relevant data protection laws. If, however you wish to raise a complaint regarding the processing of your personal data or are unsatisfied with how we have handled your information, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioners Office, the supervisory authority. If you feel we’ve said/done/got something wrong, please tell us. Contacting Us If you would like to ask anything about this policy, or anything about our workforce management products and services, you can contact us here: Call:
01942 272061
Email:
sales@addtimerecording.co.uk
Visit: Addtime Recording Company LTD UK, 358 Garswood Road, Garswood, Ashton-in-Makerfield, Wigan, WN4 0TZ
Get In Touch Addtime Recording Company LTD UK, 358 Garswood Road, Garswood, Ashton-in-Makerfield, Wigan, WN4 0TZ
01942 272061
sales@addtimerecording.co.uk
Social Media
Useful InformationTime and Attendance Software Human Resource Software Absence Management Software Mobile Clocking Systems Biometric Access Control Systems
Google Rating 5.0
Addtime
5.0
Based on 3 reviews
×
Simon Birchall 12:47 14 Aug 19
Worked with this company for 20+ years. Specialists in time management systems...
Mark Roach 15:56 20 Jun 19
We have recently migrated from a manual clock card system to the Addtime Platinum Enterprise workforce management ...
software.I would highly recommend the product and rate highly the team at Addtime and their professionalism, throughout the process of selling us the benefits of the solution, to assisting in design and implementation of it.M RoachFinance DirectorGeorge Roberts (North West) Ltdread more
GARY BARKER 16:08 19 Jun 19
I have had dealings with Tim at Add-Time for just over a year now and he is a pleasure to deal with and always goes out...
of his way to accommodate our needs. I cannot speak highly enough and would 100% recommend this company.read more
See All Reviews
Latest News
Use Attendance Software to Manage Teams RemotelyNovember 25, 2020 Best ways to Track Time for Remote WorkingNovember 20, 2020
Further InformationRemote Support Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions Sitemap
Home Products
Software
Time and Attendance Workforce Management Visitor Management Security Patrol TS4 System
Hardware
Biometric Facial Recognition Scanners Biometric Fingerprint Scanners Biometric Hand Scanners Palm Vein Scanners Proximity Card Readers
Project Management Biometric Enrolment Training Support Packages Finance Options
About Us
Meet The Team What is Time and Attendance? What is Workforce Management? Solutions for Sectors FAQ’s Our Customers Blogs Case Studies
Shop Contact
Close
